Southwest Folklore Center Sound Disc Collection, 1945-1987
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- The Liar's hour, Moore, Bill and Travis Edmonson, Cortaro, AZ., Latigo Records; 1 sound disc, analog, 33 1/3 rpm, 12 in.; Performed by Bill Moore and Travis Edmonson... The Liar's hour... Another copy of SWF 84.14/D.1... The liar's hour -- Sieery Petes -- Rye whiskey -- Boastful Bill -- The dude wrangler -- High chin Bob -- Ole Red -- Hell in Texas -- La Vaquilla Colorado -- The Bronco with wings -- The cowboy and the shepherd -- Judgement day -- Little Joe, the wrangler -- Ghost Canyon trail -- Yavapai Pete -- Lopin along -- Real cowboy life -- Ridge runnin' roan -- The old nighthawk -- Ride around --; SWF 94.19/D.1 (12in.)
- Singin' Sam's Saddlebag of Songs, Agins, Singin' Sam, Haywire Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 33 1/3 rpm, 12 in.; Performed by Singin' Sam Agins... Introduction -- Little Joe the wrangler -- Old Chisolm Trail -- Siree Peaks -- City boarders -- Punchin' the dough -- 10,000 years ago -- Hairtrigger newt -- Rawhide rope -- Jake and Rony -- Strawberry roan (parody) -- Plink plunk -- Red River Valley --; SWF 94.20/D.1 (12 in.)
- Singin' Sam and friends, Agins, Singin' Sam, West Sedona, Ariz., Haywire Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 33 1/3 rpm, 12 in.; Performed by Singin' Sam Agins... Philadelphia lawyer -- Peon named Pancho -- Had but fifty cents -- Dearly beloved -- Good old mountain dew -- Silver haired daddy -- Cowboy Nick -- South coast -- Goin' back -- Iron pants Pete -- Cat came back -- Red elk --; SWF 94.20/D.2 (12 in.)
- Triple C Chuckwagon Stage Show, Triple C Chuckwagon, [Tucson, Ariz.], Produced by Chuck Camp; 1 sound disc, analog, 33 1/3 rpm, 12 in.; Performed by the Camp family... As recorded live at the Triple C Ranch... Orange blossom special -- Introductions -- Trail dreamin; -- Ghost riders in the sky -- Tyin' knots in the devil's tail -- Alpine cowboy -- Whoopi-ti-yi-yo -- Wayward wind -- El rancho grande -- Momma don't allow -- Navajo trail -- Mountain dew -- Sagebrush in heaven -- Goodnight --; SWF 94.21/D.1 (12 in.)
- An evening at the Chuckwagon suppers, Triple C Ranch Stage Show, Tucson, Ariz., Produced by Triple C Recordings; 1 sound disc, analog, 33 1/3 rpm, 12 in.; Performed by the Camp family... Boil them cabbage down -- Way out there -- Come and get it -- Tumbling tumbleweeds -- Cool water -- Texas plains -- The Lillies grow high -- Orange blossom special -- Streets of Laredo -- It had to be you -- Mama don't allow -- In Arizona -- Silent trails -- Who spit tobacco -- Adobe hacienda -- Sage brush in heaven -- Happy rovin' cowboy --; SWF 94.21/D.2 (12 in.)
- Putting the western back in the country, The Camp Family, 1981; Tucson, Ariz., Produced by Triple C Recordings, c1981; 1 sound disc, analog, 33 1/3 rpm, 12 in.; Performed by the Camp family... Saddle up -- Navajo trail -- One more ride -- Rodeo cowboy -- Riders in the sky -- Texas plains -- Sierry Petes -- Western medley -- Blue prairie -- When payday rolls around -- Way out there -- Trail dreaming -- Ragtime cowboy Joe -- An Indian prayer -- Tumbling weeds -- El rancho grande -- Orange blossom special -- The Santa Fe trail -- San Antone Rose -- Cimmarron --; SWF 94.21/D.3 (12 in.)
- Black mountain blues, Keith, Leslie, 1974; Tucson, Ariz., Produced by Triple C Recordings, c1981; 1 sound disc, analog, 33 1/3 rpm, 12 in.; Performed by Leslie Keith, fiddle; Leonard Berline, guitar; John Hickman, banjo; Roger Bush, bass; Tom Ford, guitar; Bill Rondstadt, bass... Recorded in Tucson, Ariz... Produced by John Delgado... Cotton eyed Joe -- Black mountain blues -- Natural bridge blues -- Peacock rag -- Cacklin' hen -- Bound to ride -- Clinch mountain blues -- Bonoparte's retreat -- Lee highway blues -- Amazing Grace -- Crazy blues -- Wildcat blues -- Where the old red river flows -- Stormy waters --; SWF 94.22/D.1 (12 in.)
- The Old Country Church, Dad and Mom Poling, Tucson, Ariz., R.E.M. Records; 1 sound disc, 33 1/3 rpm, 12 in.; Performed by Orris and Ruth Polling; Bob Scott, guitar and bass; Bill Hagara, accordion and engineer. Produced by Bob Scott Frick and Bill Hagara... Some wonderful day -- My beautiful home -- The masters bouquet -- Lord build me a cabin -- The world is not my home -- Angry words -- My cottage home -- Lifes railroad to heaven -- Old country church.; SWF 95.12/D.5
- Summer Dog, Summer Dog, 1978; Tucson, Ariz., M and I Records, 1978; 1 sound disc, 33 1/3 rpm, 12 in.; NOTES: Performed by John Ross, Mandolin and baritone; Ron Doering, guitar, lead vocals, percussion, first mandolin, bass; Marc Rennard, fiddles, baritone vocals, guitar, bass; Chip Curry, banjo, tenor vocal. Recorded at Westwood Studios, Tucson, Ariz. Produced by E.C. Creigh and R.W. Doering. Making quite a living -- Twin oaks -- Special rhyme -- Shovel tooth -- Black smoke -- Riverside slide -- Coco loco -- Lonely lines of distance -- Emilia rag -- Got the feeling --; SWF 95.12/D.6
- Blue Grass by Summer Dog Band, Summer Dog, 1978; Palo Alto, Calif., Peek Publications, 1978; 1 sound disc, 33 1/3 rpm, 12 in.; NOTES: Performed by Chip Curry, banjo; Ron Doering, guitar; Marc Rennard, fiddle; Jon Ross, mandolin. Produced by Chip Curry. Recorded in Tucson, Ariz.... 12 miles and 100 years -- New money -- Beaumont rag -- Wah hoo -- Walkin' in my sleep -- Fiddle medley -- Eddie's reel -- Rawhide -- Cherokee shuffle -- The story of whistlin' Rufus -- Ragtime Annie -- Farewell blues; SWF 95.12/D.7
- The Arizona Mountaineers ... At Home, The Arizona Mountaineers, Tucson, Ariz., B.I.R.C. Records; 1 sound disc, 33-1/3 rpm, 12 in.; Performed by Don "Hardtimes" Matlock, guitar; Don "Horsefly" Johnson, fiddle; Phil "Windy" Egleston, banjo; Fred "Shortcut" Eaton, bass... Recorded in Tucson,Ariz... (I’m using my Bible) For a road map -- Homestead on the farm -- Swattin' the fly -- The last thing on my mind -- Katey Daley -- Phil's folly --Bed of roses -- San Antonio rose -- Black Mountain rag -- Good hearted woman -- Foggy mountain breakdown -- Is anybody going to San Antone -- Maiden’s prayer -- Columbus stockade blues -- I’ll always be glad to take you back -- ruby -- Orange blossom special.; SWF 95.12/D.8
- Panhandle Country, The Traditional Bluegrass [?], Phoenix, Ariz., Soundtech Studios; 1 sound disc, analog, 33 1/3 rpm, 12 in.; NOTES: Performed by Doug Piper, guitar and vocals; Howard Mathews, fiddle, bass, and vocals; Dewayne Price, banjo and high tenor vocal; Don Corley, bass and baritone vocal... Panhandle country -- Gold watch and chain -- Here I am drunk again -- Hit parade of love -- God gave you to me -- Train 45 -- Walking shoes -- Home run man -- Living like a fool -- Pike county breakdown -- Cuckoo bird -- I'm using my bible for a road map --; SWF 95.12/D.9
- Chester James... Looking Back, Chester James, Phoenix, Ariz., Reel Sound Recording Studio; 1 sound disc, analog, 33 1/3 rpm, 12 in.; NOTES: Performed by Chester James, rythm guitar; Dan Igor Glenn, string bass, dobro, autoharp, and lead guitar; Sol Rudnick, fiddle on "Blue Ridge mountain home"; Pat White, piano on "Hills of old Kentucky"... Recorded in Phoenix, Ariz... Whippoorwill song -- Bonnie wee lassie -- Two little girls in blue -- The huckster wagon -- Little whitewashed chimney -- Scarlot ribbons -- The light in the parlor -- Little alpine goat boy -- Little Joe -- The mountain of my life -- Old red cradle -- Little Shoes -- Little mother of the hills -- Little shirt mother made for me -- Blue Ridge mountain home -- Hills of old Kentucky --; SWF 95.12/D.10
- The Crucifixion of Jesus Christ, Lewis, Chuck, Tucson, Ariz., R.E.F. Records; 1 sound disc, analog, 33 1/3 rpm, 12 in.; NOTES: Performed by Chuck Lewis, voice and guitar; Bob Scott Frick, guitar, bass, and engineer... When we all get to heaven -- The crucifixion of Jesus Christ -- Old camp meeting in the sky -- I'll fly away -- Jesus is still with me -- The lily of the valley -- Turn your radio on -- This world is not my home -- Grace covers all -- Tear stains in the sand.; SWF 95.12/D.11
- Mujeriego -- La television, Guerrero, Lalo con el Mariachi Los Reyes, Los Angeles, Calif., Colonial; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Lalo Guerrero con el Mariachi Los Reyes...Mujeriego -- La television --; SWF 95.13/D.1
- Dulce madre -- Los Angeles, Guerrero, Lalo con el Mariachi Los Reyes, Los Angeles, Calif., Colonial; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Lalo Guerrero con el Mariachi Los Reyes... Dulce madre -- Los Angeles --; SWF 95.13/D.2
- El Paso -- El ultima tiro, Guerrero, Lalo con los Tajuarines, Monterey Park, Calif., Colonial; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Lalo Guerrero con los Tajuarines... El Paso -- El ultima tiro --; SWF 95.13/D.3
- Idolo de oro -- El burro norteño, Guerreo, Lalo con el Mariachi los Camperas, Monterey Park, Calif., Colonial; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Lalo Guerrero con el Mariachi los Camperos... Idolo de oro -- El burro norteño --; SWF 95.13/D.4
- Carta de un bracero -- Las Posadas, Guerrero, Lalo con el Mariachi los Camperas, Monterey Park, Ca., Colonial; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Lalo Guerrero con el Mariachi los Camperos... Carta de un bracero -- Las Posadas --; SWF 95.13/D.5
- Carta de un soldad -- El corrido de Deleno, Guerrero, Lalo con el Conjunto Arellano, Monterey Park, Ca., Colonial Discos Latinos; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Lalo Guerrero con el Cojunto Arellano... Carta de un soldado -- El corrido de Deleno --; SWF 95.13/D.6
- Pancho Clause -- The burrito, Guerrero, Lalo, Cap Latino; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Lalo Guerrero... Pancho Clause -- The burrito --; SWF 95.13/D.7
- La minifalda de Reynalda -- Lagrimas de borracha, Guerrero, Lalo con el Conjunto Arellano, Garden, Ca., Colonial Discos Latinos; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Lalo Guerrero con el Conjunto Arellano... La minifalda de Reynalda -- Lagrimas de borracha --; SWF 95.13/D.8
- La celosa -- Felipe el hippie, Guerrero, Lalo con Mimi Reyes, Monterey Park, Ca., Colonial Discos Latinos; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Lalo Guerrero con Mimi Rogers y el Conjunto Arellano... La celosa -- Felipe el hippie --; SWF 95.13/D.9
- Ya supe, Lupe -- Lamento de soltero, Guerrero, Lalo con el Conjunto Arellano, Monterey Park, Ca., Colonial Discos Latinos; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Lalo Guerrero con el Conjunto Arellano... Ya supe, Lupe -- Lamento del soltero --; SWF 95.13/D.10
- La tragedia del 29 de agosto -- Homenaye a Ruben Salazar, Guerrero, Lalo con el Conjunto de los Hermanos Quezada, Monterey Park, Ca., Colonial Discos Latinos; 1 sound disc, ananlog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Lalo Guerrero con el Conjunto de los Hermanos Quezada... La tragedia del 29 de agosto -- Homenaye a Ruben Salazar --; SWF 95.13/D.11
- Pancho Claus -- Paisano in a piñon tree, McCarthy, Jacki, 1981; Santa Fe, N.M., Paisano Music Production, 1981; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Jacki "La Gringa" McCarthy with the "Mariachis América"... Pancho Claus -- Paisano in a piñon tree --; SWF 95.13/D.12
- Las botellas de licor -- En tu cas no me quieren, Guerrero, Lalo, Monterey Park, Ca., Discos Clave; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Lalo Guerrero... Las botellas de licor -- En tu casa no me quieren --; SWF 95.13/D.13
- El remate -- Ema, la de autocinema, Guerrero, Lalo con el Conjunto de los Hermanos Quezada, Monterey Park, Ca., Discos Clave; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Lalo Guerrero con el Conjunto de los Hermanos Quezada... El remate -- Ema, la de autocinema --; SWF 95.13/D.14
- Juana, Tacha, y Chona -- Sinverguenza mantenido, Guerrero, Lalo con la Orquesta de Noe Falcon, Monterey Park, Ca., Discos Clave; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Lalo Guerrero con la Orquesta de Noe Falcon and Irene Brunilda... Juanan, Tacha, y Chona -- Sinverguenza mantenido --; SWF 95.13/D.15
- Juana, Tacha, y Chona -- Sinverguenza mantenido, Guerrero, Lalo and Irene Brunilda, Albuquerque, N.M., Cristy Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Lalo Guerrero and Irene Brunilda con la Orquesta de Noe Falcon... Juana, Tacha, y Chana -- Sinverguenza mantenido --; SWF 95.13/D.15(2)
- Un nuevo amor -- Que vuelvan los braceros, Guerrero, Lalo con el Conjunto de los Hermanos Arellano, Mexico, Musart; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Lalo Guerrero con el Conjunto de los Hermanos Arellano... Un nuevo amor -- Que vuelvan los braceros --; 95.13/D.16
- Señor sueño -- Espinita, Guerrero, Lalo con Orquesta Real, Pasadena, Ca., Real Record Co.; 1 sound disc, ananlog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Lalo Guerrero con Orquesta Real... Señor sueño -- Espinita --; SWF 95.13/D.17
- Somos amigos -- Quico el buen chico, Guerrero, Lalo con Quico y Ardillitas, Mexico, EMI Capitol; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm 7 in.; NOTES: Performed Quico y Ardillitas de Lalo Guerrero... Somos Amigos -- Quico el buen chico --; SWF 95.13/D.18
- La Risa -- El violin, Guerrero, Lalo con las Ardillitas, Mexico, EMI; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Lalo Guerrero con las Ardillitas... La Risa -- El violin --; SWF 95.13/D.19
- Los ilegales -- El chicano, Guerrero, Lalo, Mexico, Discos Latin International; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Lalo Guerrero... Los ilegales -- El chicano --; SWF 95.13/D.20
- ¡Ole! Fernando -- Fernando el toro, Guerrero, Lalo and the Mariachi Sol de Mexico, 1981; Los Angeles, Ca., Ambiente Productions, 1981; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTE: Performed by Lalo Guerrero and the Mariachi Sol de Mexico; Esteban Hernandez, violin; Jésus Hernández, guitar; Humberto Hernández, vihuela; Francisco "Capiro" Castro, guitarron; José Hernández, trumpet... Produced by Philip Sonnichsen... ¡Ole! Fernando -- Fernando el toro --; SWF 95.13/D.21
- La mula bronca -- En donde esta el corazon, Garcia, Lalo y su Conjunto, Mexico, Discos CBS; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Lalo Garcia y su Conjunto... La mula bronca -- En donde esta el corazon --; SWF 95.13/D.22
- El corre caminos -- Panfilo para presidente, Guerrero, Lalo con el Mariachi Los Camperos, Mexico, Discos Peerless; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Lalo Guerrero con el Mariachi Los Camperos... El corre caminos -- Panfilo para presidente --; SWF 95.13/D.23
- Juan Charrasqueado -- Virgencita milagrosa, Trio Imperial, Los Angeles, Ca., Imperial Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; NOTES: Performed by Trio Imperial: Lalo, Mario, y José... Juan Charrasqueado -- Virgencita milagrosa --; SWF 95.13/D.24
- La nueva generacion -- Corrido mexicano, Trio Imperial, Los Angeles, Ca., Imperial Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; NOTES: Performed by Trio Imperial: Lalo, Mario, y José... La nueva generacion -- Corrido mexicano --; SWF 95.13/D.25
- El pachuco -- Siempre traes a tu mama, Trio Imperial, Los Angeles, Ca., Imperial Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; NOTES: Performed by Trio Imperial: Lalo, Mario, y José... El pachuco -- Siempre traes a tu mama --; SWF 95.13/D.26
- El Pachuco y el Tarzan -- Pa' luego es tarde, Trio Imperial, Los Angeles, Ca., Imperial Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; NOTES: Performed by Trio Imperial: Lalo, Mario, y José... El Pachuco y el Tarzan -- Pa' Luego es tarde --; SWF 95.13/D.27
- Las comadres pachucas -- Mujeres apachucadas, Trio Imperial, Los Angeles, Ca., Imperial Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; NOTES: Performed by Trio Imperial... Las comadres pachucas -- Mujeres apachucadas --; SWF 95.13/D.28
- Ten cuidado -- La cotorrona, Trio Imperial, Los Angeles, Ca., Imperial Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; NOTES: Performed by Trio Imperial... Ten cuidado -- La cotorrona --; SWF 95.13/D.29
- La gallinita -- Tu libertad, Trio Imperial, Los Angeles, Ca., Imperial Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; NOTES: Performed by Trio Imperial... La gallinita -- Tu libertad --; SWF 95.13/D.30
- Ya volvio rl soldado raso -- Quien será mi rival, Guerrero, Lalo con el Mariachi de Rafael Arredondo, Los Angeles, Ca., Imperial Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; NOTES: Performed by Lalo Guerrero con el Mariachi de Rafael Arredondo... Ya volvio el soldado raso -- Quien será mi rival --; SWF 95.13/D.31
- La culebra pollera -- El alacrán, Guerrero, Lalo con el Mariachi de Francisco Rodriguez, Hollywood, Ca., Imperial Record Co. Inc.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; NOTES: Performed by Lalo Guerrero con el Mariachi de Francisco Rodriguez... La culebra pollera -- El alacrán --; SWF 95.13/D.32
- Mis cinco novias -- El soldado, Guerrero, Lalo con el Conjunto Luis B. Hijar, Hollywood, Ca., Imperial Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; NOTES: Performed by Lalo Guerrero con el Conjunto Luis B. Hijar... Mis cinco novias -- El soldado --; SWF 95.13/D.33
- Corrido de Pedro infante -- Me cais como anillo al dedo, Guerrero, Lalo con el Mariachi Reyes de Chapala, Los Angeles, Ca., Colonial; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; NOTES: Performed by Lalo Guerrero con el Mariachi Reyes de Chapala... Corrido de Pedro infante -- Me cais como anillo al dedo --; SWF 95.13/D.34
- Pancho Lopez -- Vengo a despertarte, Los Dos Reales con el Mariachi Vargas de Teclitlan, Mexico, RCA Records; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; NOTES: Performed by Los Dos Reales con el Mariachi Vargas de Tecalitlan... Pancho Lopez -- Vengo a despertarte --; SWF 95.13/D.35
- Guerrero, Lalo, Guerrero, Lalo, 1976; Mexico, EMI Capitol, 1976; 1 sound disc, analog, 33 1/3 rpm, 12 in.; NOTES: Performed by Lalo Guerrero... Oigo una banda -- Enamorado de ti -- No me gusta dormir solo -- Porque te quiero, no lo se -- Ya -- Con todo el corazon -- No me quedo llorando -- Mayo y deciembre -- A pesar de todo -- Vamos a bailar --; SWF 95.13/D.36
- Houston Blues -- The grass won't pay no mind, Lambert, Burt and the Northern Express, 1977; Phoenix, Ariz., Canyon Records, 1977; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Burt Lambert and the Northern Express; Roland Gourneau; Lancelot Azure; Mike Hawley; Kathy Moran; Wanda Moran... Houston Blues -- The grass won't pay no mind --; SWF 95.15/D.1
- Love me or leave me -- Granite city blues, Country, Francis, Jr., 1978; Phoenix, Ariz., Canyon Records, 1978; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by: Francis Country Jr., lead guitar; Jeff Country, bass guitar; Dennis Enoch, drums... Love me or leave me -- Granite city blues --; SWF 95.15/D.2
- Truquero polka -- Cosita linda-cumbia, Kelly, Elvin y los Reyes, 1972; Phoenix, Ariz., Canyon Records, 1972; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Elvin Kelly y los Reyes; Elvin Kelly, sax; Steve Kelly, drums; Elmer Ray, sax; Harry Ray, guitar; Kenneth Antone, bass guitar... Truquero polka -- Cosita linda-cumbia --; SWF 95.15/D.3
- Too late now -- Oklahoma trail, Cassa, Murphey, Phoenix, Ariz., Canyon Records; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Murphey Cassa, drum... Too late now -- Oklahoma trail --; SWF 95.15/D.4
- Davis Talewiftema's buffalo dance song -- David Talewiftema's butterfly dance song, Hopi Singers from Second Mesa, Phoenix, Ariz., Canyon Records; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Hopi Singers from Second Mesa, led by David Talewiftema... David Talewiftema's buffalo dance song -- David Talewiftema's butterfly dance song --; SWF 95.15/D.5
- Make it two dollars -- Short skirted girlfriend, White, Kenneth, Phoenix, Ariz., Canyon Records; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Kenneth White with drum... Make it two dollars -- Short skirted girlfriend --; SWF 95.15/D.6
- Prisoner's song -- Old style Eagle dance, Lacapa, Leo, Phoenix, Ariz., Canyon Records; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Leo Lacapa with Valentino Lacapa on drums and bells... Prisoner's song -- Old style Eagle dance --; SWF 95.15/D.7
- Butterfly dance -- Zuni na-ha-li-sho, Lomawaima, Harvey / Shebaba, L., Phoenix, Ariz., Canyon Records; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Side one performed by Harvey Lomawaima and his Hopi dancers from Second Mesa, Arizona... Butterfly dance... Side two performed by L. Shebaba; Mallon; R. Gasper with drum, bells, gourd, and rain rattle... Zuni Nah-ha-li-sho --; SWF 95.15/D.8
- If you hold my hand -- Farewell song, Nez, Wilbur, Phoenix, Ariz., Canyon Records; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Wilbur Nez, solo drum... If you hold my hand -- Farewell song --; SWF 95.15/D.9
- Meet at Nob Hill -- Heart break tepee, Cheyenne Dave Group, Phoenix, Ariz., Canyon Records; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Cheyenne Dave Group with drums, bells, and whistle... Meet me at Nob Hill -- Heart break tepee --; SWF 95.15/D.10
- Sad news -- Keys in the mailbox, El Coochise, 1977; Phoenix, Ariz., Canyon Records, c1977; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by El Coochise: Chuck Tortice; Tinker Nez; Danny Snead... Sad news -- Keys in the mailbox --; SWF 95.15/D.11
- Black Jack's bar -- She's gone gone gone, Montana, Joe and the Roadrunners, Canyon Records; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Joe Montana and the Roadrunners: Hualapai Indian group from Peach Springs, Ariz.... Black Jack's bar -- She's gone gone gone --; SWF 95.15/D.13
- Be free with me -- Why can't I understand, Hamana, Bruce, 1974; Phoenix, Ariz., Canyon Records, c1974; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Bruce Hamana from the album 'Hamana'... Be free with me -- Why can't I understand --; SWF 95.15/D.14
- Dark skin woman -- Sunrise vision, Bee, Tom and Mitch Traylor, 1977; Phoenix, Ariz., Canyon Records, c1977; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Tom Bee and Mitch Traylor... Dark skin woman -- Sunrise vision --; SWF 95.15/D.15
- Pitty pitty patter -- I've got a happy heart, Crawley, Tammie Dee, Kayenta, Ariz., Diné (The people); 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Tammie Dee Crawley and The Undecided Takers... Recorded in the studios of Audio Recorder in Phoenix... Pitty pitty patter -- I've got a happy heart --; SWF 95.15/D.16
- Weekend woman -- Indian cowboy, Midnite and Lee, 1977; Whiteriver, Ariz., Apache Spirit, c1977; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Midnite and Lee... Weekend woman -- Indian cowboy --; SWF 95.15/D.17
- One more friend -- She's lookin' for a man, Midnite, 1978; Whiteriver, Ariz., Apache Spirit, c1978; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Midnite... One more friend -- She's lookin' for a man --; SWF 95.15/D.18
- Everybody's talkin at me -- Run woman run, The Moran Sisters, 1977; Phoenix, Ariz., Canyon Records, c1977; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by The Moran Sisters: Kathy, Carol, Wanda, and Judy... Everybody's talkin at me (Carol Moran, vocals) -- Run woman run (Kathy Moran, lead vocals) --; SWF 95.15/D.19
- Everything will always be together -- Keep movin' on, Midnite and Lee, 1977; Whiteriver, Ariz., Apache Spirit, c1977; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Midnite and Lee... Everything will always be together -- Keep movin' on --; SWF 95.15/D.20
- Did it go away -- The way he plays it, Lee, 1977; Whiteriver, Ariz., Apache Spirit, c1978; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; NOTES: Performed by Lee... Did it go away -- The way he plays it --; SWF 95.15/D.21